{
    "id": "172ad05b678241a3916df1b395e2e0de",
    "title": "Confusing Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Please give me a ………………… of paper.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "peace",
                "piece",
                "peas"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How much is the railway ………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fair",
                "fare"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Jane has got very …………………. looks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "plane",
                "plain",
                "plan"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "As he had no shirt, the sun burnt his ………………… . skin.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bare",
                "bear"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I really want to …………………. some weight.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lose",
                "loss",
                "loose"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "An oil lamp needs a ………………… ..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "weak",
                "week",
                "wick"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "My little brother is very …………………… so we don’t let him touch anything …………………… ..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "irresponsable breakable",
                "irresponsible breakable",
                "irresponsible breakible"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A ………………….. looks like a big rabbit.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hare",
                "hair",
                "heir"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She was unusually ………………… .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "quite",
                "quiet"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… . going to the market.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "We're",
                "Were",
                "Where"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}